[
  {
    "front": "_______ is an art movement that involves imagery dealing with Pop culture.",
    "back": "Pop Art"
  },
  {
    "front": "This artist was a major contributor to the Pop Art movement. He is most famously known for the use of repeating imagery in his work, such as Marilyn Monroe and Campbell's Soup Cans.",
    "back": "Andy Warhol"
  },
  {
    "front": "___ Lichtenstein became famous for his bold Pop Art paintings of comic stip cartoons and everyday objects.",
    "back": "Roy"
  },
  {
    "front": "Robert Rauschenberg is best known for the _______ a hybrid form of painting and sculpture that integrates humble materials, found images, and paint to bridge what he called 'the gap between art and life.'",
    "back": "combine"
  },
  {
    "front": "true or false| The main goal of the artists belonging to the Pop Art movement, was trying to question the concept of 'what art is'.",
    "back": "true"
  },
  {
    "front": "Pop Art first emerged in the mid-____s in both America and Britain.",
    "back": "1950"
  },
  {
    "front": "'Art is anything you can ___ ____ ____.' -Andy Warhol",
    "back": "get away with"
  },
  {
    "front": "Pop Art coincided with the ___ _____ movement in the 1950s and 1960s, and was always associated with it.",
    "back": "Pop Music"
  },
  {
    "front": "______, red, and blue were the predominant colors used by Pop Art artists.",
    "back": "yellow"
  },
  {
    "front": "John ______ was the first artist to use the term 'Pop Art'.",
    "back": "McHale"
  }
]